Hello, good morning, are you watching?
Hain Money Main Hoon Sandeep Grover Opening Buzz
You are very welcome to me. Thursday's
The day is the Sussex weekly expiry.
Is. But today is also a good day for the market.
It could be good. hope so. such hope
Is. After yesterday's rise, Indian today also
The momentum in the markets is positive
It can be seen only on the side. his
What is the reason? The reason why expectations are being built
It is about war. Which is related to ceasefire or
Then about stopping the war. what updates have come
Are you regarding that? What did Mr. Trump say?
What kind of talks are coming from Iran's side?
Is? And these talks that took place regarding ceasefire
or about the ceasefire, ah him
What are the updates regarding this? second round
What feelers are out there regarding the conversation?
I am coming. The market reacts to this.
It will appear to have happened and along with it some results
You will also know the impact of on Indian markets today.
I will see it. All these updates, your questions
answers, as well as the primary market
The action is in front of you in the next one and a half hour.
Will keep it. First look at tomorrow's market
That is, the mid-week session which was held on Wednesday
What we saw unfolding on Monday
After the fall in the markets, if tomorrow
You will see that the Wednesday market
The market was recovering from Monday's decline.
It appeared to be happening and Nifty crossed 24,200.
It appeared to be closing. 24,281 This is our
It was an intraday high. This is the Wednesday market
Is. There was a holiday on Tuesday. We also updated
I made a mistake in doing it. So what is 24,281?
It was an intraday high, from there we are down about 50%
Seen closing down. But overall look
If we go, we have also counted 24,300 once.
I tried but I couldn't pass it.
Get him. So the 45 stocks of Nifty are
Indigo and Par Grid have climbed to the top
Were the gainers and highest point wise
As far as contribution is concerned, he is a giant
Reliance Industries, LNT, HDFC Bank and
Infosys had a major contribution in its growth.
The one-day decline in Bank Nifty also stopped.
Exactly at 56,300 level at 56,299
You can say that closing happened around here. Day
We also attempted 56,800 during
Was. 56,786 was our intraday high.
From there we reached almost 500 points.
Lightened and closed. But still 56300
We saw the settlement around . Nifty
Almost 400 points up. In Sussex
There was strength of more than 1250 points.
Nifty gains almost 700 points
The bank also managed to close. someone like
Sector indices were not in the red yesterday.
There was a mark. The capital market index
Broking is a stock market related business.
or exchanges have a 3.5%
The [music] jump in the index we saw yesterday
It was seen being made. Apart from this, tourism, IT,
Realty, Defense, Oil Gas, Media Energy,
PS2 Index This was also seen running away yesterday.
You can see the advance decline of almost 7:1.
Was from nearby. Mid-cap index 2.5% and
Small cap index and more than 2.5%
It appeared to be closing strongly. Brand
The price fell to around $95. So
You can see a gain of 3 to 6% in OMC shares.
Closing was strong. stock
If you look at the specifics, the share of Retail will increase tomorrow.
18.5% ran. They will get ₹565 from RBNL
A new order worth around Rs. crore has been received.
Apart from this, if you look at Bank of America
Coverage has been initiated with a Buy rating.
We saw tremendous growth in Groww stock yesterday.
The action seems to be building on the positive side
Was. If you talk about growth, then tomorrow
We saw a gain of 4 to 5% in the stock during the session.
It is an upmove, it was seen being made and 7% in fact
The stock was seen closing with strength.
As far as the impact of Q4 results is concerned
So we saw that ICIC Potential Life
rose 2% but ICICI Potential AMC
It saw a decline of 4% after the results.
Got it. LIC announces 1:1 bonus
of. After the market closes on Monday evening
After yesterday we saw a gain of 5% in the stock
And Indus Towers took a downgrade
Ratings and targets also came from Jefferies.
has also been cut. See its impact
The stock has gained 5.25% even in a strong market.
The surroundings were seen to be declining. And one more
The stock was falling, that haven Small Finance
Of the bank. Universal Banking License
For which he has applied to RBI
She has come back. to the loan book
RBI has talked about diversifying
on behalf of. The market did not like this.
This stock is also trading up by around 3% in a strong market.
Closed with a decline of around Rs. Let's go to tomorrow
You understood the action. how are you today
You can see the market reacting.
Please show me the gift Nifty once. then further
We will continue to update you and let you know when we get updates.
What are you coming? the conversation that is about to take place
Regarding that between the US and Iran. 24
237 was the level where our Nifty was yesterday
24,240 if the futures close
I'll go with the round figure and 24,320
If you see the level in Gift Nifty
So there is a gap up of around 80 points
Seen in Indian markets today
Can. Tomorrow almost around 400 points
We have seen similar gains on Nifty. 24,300
We had attempted this and it could have happened today.
that we should also attempt 24,300,
Cross it and try to stay on it.
Try to see the market and see
Will also try to survive. So for the Bulls
Today's resistance is 24,300.
Resistance exists because it cannot be overcome
It is becoming a little difficult to do.
Will it cross today? This is largely
It will depend on the global market
What kind of signals are there and how can this war be
What is the update regarding this? Talking about all this
Are. My colleague Narendra joins me.
Have already done. You are most welcome Narendra.
Very good morning. First, tell me this
that these talks are going to happen regarding this
All kinds of things are going on. Different
The feelers are coming. from different sources
News is coming. What is the update to the conversation?
Taking? Tell me that first.
Yes, good morning Sandeep. If the conversation
If we talk about the talks between the US and Iran
So at the moment there is no one regarding this
There is no clarity. Although it is believed that
that there is a hurry between these two
A second round of talks may take place. of the US
blockade of the hormone state from the side at the moment
What is happening now is ongoing and the US has consistently
The hormone state is blocked. And
Also, hormones without the US of Europe
A report also appeared on the security alliance
The news has come quoting. Iranians also
Iran continues its blockade of ports
has also threatened the US. Iran has said that
It covers the Persian Gulf, the Sea of ​​Oman, and the Red Sea.
Can block. If Hormos State of
Hormone blockade if continued
doing. Apart from this, whatever is white regarding this
Many statements have also come from the House. The White House
Tried to increase ceasefire. to the news
rejected and furthermore with Iran
He said that his relations with Iran
The talks are still ongoing and China
Banks received some letters from the US Treasury
and it said in this the US Treasury
The Secretary has said that if money from Iran
If a flow of Rs 1000 is found, they can be banned.
Is. Apart from this, White House President
The Secretary said that the President's
It is in Iran's interest to meet the demands
And they should complete it. Whereas the next round
Pakistan is expected to be the venue for
There is a very high possibility. This is also the White House
This is the statement of the President's Secretary. Its
Apart from this, the US Study Secretary said that we
General on Russian oil and Iranian oil oil
Will not renew license. So the rhetoric
It is coming from both sides. But the second round
When will the talks begin? Regarding this
At present, no clarity has been received.
Yes.
Ok. So there's a lot that can be discussed.
Is. In Pakistan, there may be others
There may be a round of talks. But now some
It is not final. What did Mr. Trump do in the meantime?
Said? Mr. Trump's statement is very important.
to which the markets also react
Are.
Yes Sandeep Trump sir, this is happening continuously every day
Are giving statement. He still made the statement
Gave statement. He said the Iran war
is very close to its end and Iran is very
Wants to deal with them badly.
Although President Trump is
He has given this statement many times before and this
And this time again he gives a statement like this.
Have been. Apart from this, what is there on tooth social
Trump remains active and there too
He has given his statement. he said
that China is very happy that I am from Hormoz State
I am opening it forever. I do this to their
I am doing it for myself and for the world as well. Such
The condition will never happen again. He to Iran
Have agreed not to send weapons. When
I'll be there in a few weeks.
President Xi will give me a big hug.
Let me tell you that the President
President President, which is Trump and Xi
There are also talks about Jinping's meeting
There is also talk of a meeting and whatever
Trump goes to China and meets Xi Jinping
You can meet him from. He said we are together
Working smarter and better together
Are doing. Is this fight better than fighting?
Not there. But remember if we fight we
If we have to fight, we are very good at it.
Are. Far better than anyone else. So this is what
This is Trump's statement. So you said this to him
It can also be called an inflammatory statement or one which
Trump often brags about the manner in which he
He also shared this on his Truth Social.
He has made statements in this manner. Yes
So, it is clear somewhere that this
The target is not Iran. target
There is China and look at the state of China
There has been talk of opening hormones, he says this
They are saying that I opened it for China also.
For the world, this is the state of hormones.
It has just been opened. Now here's an update on Iran.
Narendra Bhai was studying. So they are saying this
I was thinking that this is a conversation and I should not put my conditions on it.
Pressure to agree is not a conversation
It would have been. Perhaps this was the reason why the first round was
There was no result in the hour that passed.
No, he came out in front. So, Mr. Trump
Do you want to surround us by creating pressure?
By imposing a blockade, he imposed his conditions.
They want to convince him because he lost the war.
Have already done. One thing is clear. He is his
By agreeing to the conversation, they want to prove that
The US won this war because so many
This war had to end soon and the war was over.
In a hurry to do it and on your terms
By getting it made, somewhere or the other, you and your
I want to assure the countrymen that
That we have won this war. restored in the meantime
How Global Markets Are Reacting
Naveen brother of this
If we talk about global markets,
The hope for the second round of talks
Because of what is happening in the global markets today
There is a boom being seen. Asian markets
If we talk about Nikke then there are approximately 22 more
Hang Seng is trading up about 1p.
Apart from this, there is also some important data of China.
Have come. China's GDP growth in Q4
It has increased from 4.5% to 5%. Ah
Apart from this, China's retail sales in March
Which is 1.7%
and industrial output 5.7%
Has increased. And talking about American markets
If we look at it, the US markets closed mixed yesterday.
Has happened. A modest 72 points in double figures
A decline has been observed. But the SNB 500
and Nesdc closing at record highs tomorrow
Have succeeded in. In addition, the dollar
The index is seeing a decline
and it is 97.99
Currently trading around the level of
Is. Whereas in the US, 10-year bond yield
There is a rise in and 4.27%
It is doing business around Rs. Its
Apart from this, European markets closed mixed yesterday.
And yesterday there was a light of 22 points in the dex
An increase has been seen. Whereas the US and Iran
with the possibility of renegotiation
Currently, the business within the brand scope
It is seen doing so and its price is 95.27
Built around the barrel. There itself
Range bound trading in gold and silver too
It is visible. Gold $484 per ounce
And silver is currently around $80 per ounce.
Is doing business. Yes
OK, so the US markets are closed.
Has happened. NASDC SNP you are saying that
closed at record highs and China's
The GDP growth numbers that have come are also
You have come well. So are Asian markets.
Reacting positively today. So
Expect today after yesterday's strength
Another positive in Indian markets
The session can be seen. Thank you very much
Your brother, we receive this complete update.
To deliver. So there is no clarity yet.
When will the second round of talks take place and where?
Will happen. Although the fears are such that very soon
Maybe another one in Pakistan
A round of talks that can be conducted
Yes, and Mr. Trump has already said that
The war is over, now it's time for negotiations.
[sound of clearing throat] That's what it's going to be
Conditions, when and how, from which country
considered or the phase of negotiations
whether or not consensus can be reached on it
It can be made. Meanwhile, you can watch FI tomorrow.
Went on with purchases worth ₹66 crore in the session
Net Net and DI have seen the opportunity
Has taken sales of around ₹570 crore
has done. Let's go over all this data and the whole mood
An atmosphere is being created for discussion on the war.
We do. We have a special guest with us.
Are. Market Patterns with us Avinash
Kurkshekar ji has joined the program
Are. Very good morning sir. very welcome
Is your money on the line?
Yes, good morning Sandeep.
Sir, this whole mood and atmosphere that is being created in Iran
The whole conversation that's coming out about Trump
You must have seen all the statements of the Sahib. meanwhile
Sir, what is happening in the market now?
Should positioning be done? Is this the value of
Let's say the war is over. Now the conversation
It remains who bends to what extent and to whom
What does negotiation entail and how is consensus reached?
No, definitely watch it, I think war
Which was earlier feared would last long. My
I think whatever Mr. Trump has right now
attitude, one thing is clear from this that he
are also looking towards conversations and sessions and
Such reports have come out after the first round.
That's probably the second round of you coming in
There will be no discussion. look somewhere
The market also liked this thing. Tomorrow
The market has shown a very good bounce.
Nifty closed down by around 400 points yesterday.
And for the first time, FI also did a little bit
Have made a purchase. So I feel that
Look at the market now back to fundamentals and
Will focus on earnings. Even today, large
There are results of companies. Was there yesterday also. so me
It seems the results season is going quite well right now.
It has started. Whatever the results of the companies
I think he has come so far and is very fat.
The big markets have liked it a lot. And
This is what you will see in the market today.
Will get it. Although today the opening is 70-80 points
Nifty is showing that it will open. But my
Stock Specific Approach with Care
It will remain important because where the earning
The management of the company will also be good.
There will be good commentary on the markets there.
There should be more focus. index me
It seems to remain in a small range and
Talk about the overall geopolitical situation.
So I think it will happen in the next 15-20 days.
It is possible that a proper session may emerge but
I think your main focus right now is
I think you know corporate earnings
This will remain the same which I think investors will
You should focus. Ok. So in the market sir
What should be the direction? How to trade
Should I or how should I make a strategy?
Look, I think Broadley Markets
Will remain on the higher side because right now the market
The panickers have left. I think that
There are a few sectors like auto, auto
There are components, then capital goods, then
Hotels are hospitality. I think that
These are the domestic facing sectors here
Focus on it. There are still plenty of opportunities here
You will get good large cap and mid cap
In. I think I am good at IT too.
Value is being created because TCS
The numbers have come out quite good. My thoughts
In such a difficult environment, he achieved the number
Showed it properly. So somehow I think
That the market is looking at these sectors more
Will show no positivity. Metals are also a
It is a good sector which may be in March
Very strong numbers in the quarter, you will get these
Seen in the companies of the sector. So
In the few sectors that I have mentioned
Focus. What we see in a large cap company
I like that Mahindra in auto. Capital
Goods in Lasan and to go have you no hotel
If there are Indian hotels in the sector then somewhere
If you look at market numbers somewhere, then here
Focus and I think you have no bias.
Stay positive, there is no hurry to go short
Don't do
So auto capital goods hotels and what
You said sectors, sir.
Sir, I said you have capital goods.
Then after that you also have no power equipment.
Hotel can also be a power generation facility.
After that, auto auto auto components, all these
Sectors
Okay, so auto, capital goods, hotels, power.
And auto components you can buy more on these
Focus on some stocks that have also been mentioned to you.
Like LAT or MNM, these
But you should focus more on large caps.
You should pay more attention to this, sir.
If I may ask you a question then FIS
They are also slowly starting to return. Although
Still selling around ₹400 crore
The number is net net because in April it is heavy
We sold heavily for several days, earning Rs 80,000 crore.
Have you seen it? But Sir, this 666 crores yesterday
The number has come, looking at this ah ah this
The second number is Sir, 10 in this month itself
April was also the year for purchases. That means that
Of Friday's session. So now, Sir,
According to you, if someone has ₹100
How much money did it take to invest in the market?
should give?
No, I still think 2530%
It should only be applied. Look Sandeep, still
There is no complete clarity in the market
Because Mr. Trump is still in a mood
Can change at any time and some negative
If you say so, the market will give it a negative response.
If you take it then I would say that you can take 25-30% right now.
Deploy and buy in chunks
Because don't be in a hurry, at some point
If you can buy everything at Rs. 1000 then this strategy probably
will come in handy because until it is completely
Until the war session is over, we
I cannot say with any guarantee that
How will the market work? No one knows how the market will work.
If a negative surprise comes, the market falls.
I think he will fall for me very quickly too
Starting with 25-30%
start with 25 to 30% okay tomorrow when
I am telling you sir, in the cash segment.
FIs have bought futures worth ₹66 crore
If we look at the market also, index futures
Some were purchased for ₹1243 crore, though
Around ₹4500 crore in index options
Stocks worth ₹93 crore are on sale
Futures are sold and stock options are traded.
Also, there was selling of around ₹900 crore.
It has happened. The net net number is ₹4,211 crore
Of selling. and in the long-short ratio
If you go and see this index
Options have been sold, some of them are long.
Unwinding has also taken place because the one with 21.82%
The long part has reduced to almost
It is seen reaching around 21%. Sir
Positioning of FI when FI is in FNO
If they were buying, they were selling for cash. Now
When buying and selling in cash, some FAO
In this we are seeing that their long
The unwinding is visible. So
Gradually, they are buying from FAO now.
Shifting positions to cash.
No, I think look at this FNO
This is a position, it keeps changing every day. But
I think somewhere this long
The ratio of the shot is little by little
Will improve when fully geopolitical
Clarity will come on the situation and bond yields
So now they have become a little soft, so these too
a good thing because as soon as Bond
Yields are soft. Lots of money back.
Will bring it to India. So I think a little
Please wait but for a day or two
No Movement gives you a complete understanding of the trend.
Will not come. After a little while, you
You know, do you understand the meaning of these numbers?
Will come. But a day or two at FAO positions
Did you get any idea after seeing the You Know trend?
Can't. So I think it's better to wait.
And watch. [nasal sound]
Ok. Ok. If we consider some household signs
If we talk, first look at the dollar rupee tomorrow.
We saw a fairly stable rupee.
There was business. Look at the closing
So it has closed with a gain of 1 paisa.
9338 with 93.37
Ah settled at the level of. Wednesday's
in session than Monday if you
If you see, Sir, at one time we had 93 rupees.
I also saw the lower levels. Even till 95 we
Had reached. The positioning that is being made now
Nor will our forex reserves
Our foreign exchange reserves are quite large.
Things are going well. But tomorrow I Sir a
I was reading the report. We are sixth in the world
You have reached the top, sir. of the Sixth World
We are now in the forefront as the largest economy.
I am coming. Where did we end up at number four?
Were. Now we have to go back to the two-three year link.
You will have to work hard. By 2028, we may be third.
He was seen reaching the top. So we
You have slipped, sir. sixth largest
in the world economy. Because this is what
The rupee has weakened, but that has affected our situation to a great extent.
The overall positioning across the world is
He seems to be getting a little hurt.
Sir, how are you looking at this and the rupee?
This is where we reached the six spot
In the world.
No, look, I think this ranking
I think this is the number, see age
Of now we are at number six. first number four
Were on. I think wait a while
If the Mach numbers improve slightly
After that our ranking will improve again.
Will go. I don't think any of this
Big negative surprise on the markets
Will come in the near term. Yes in the long term
Definitely a matter of some concern. But
I think look at the overall situation right now
Crude prices have increased in this way
Cost pressure has increased. somewhere or the other
Even an economy like India needs a little bit
You will have to suffer losses. So I think near
It is a little negative in the short term but long term
I think we need to improve
There is a lot of capacity.
Ok. One head, neither in this war environment
The thing we forgot is the trade deal.
A statement came yesterday regarding the trade deal.
Our take on the Trade Secretary
that our negotiating team
The negotiating team is ah 20 to 22
She will be on a US tour in April. India has
Joe Trade Representative of the US
Ah, also the response to his request for consultation
I have given it. So now from 20th to 22nd April is very
It will become important. Sir, the results
Also, how important is this trade deal?
for us and what about exports today
Will stocks remain in focus due to this news?
No, it's a good thing. See ultimately
somewhere or somewhere this
Progress is being made. What is the result of this now?
Does it come out? The duty at present
The structure has been given to India by the US.
How You Know Sectors Pay and You Know
Products and services pay out
Is. The market would like to see this because my
See carefully that the trade deal is finalized
It was already done. After that this Iran war started.
Went. So somewhere the market is expecting
Will someone or the other reach the final here?
The decision comes and I think then it will be
Back to Business As Usual. So definitely
This is positive news.
Okay, this is definitely positive. Its
Apart from this, Sir, a statement came from RBI yesterday.
Is. What have they done, sir?
Which branch expansion is suitable for NBFCs?
The rules have been eased off. Ah
Through a Revised Authorization Framework
If NBFCs want to expand their branches
If you want to do it then the rules are enough for that.
have been made quite easy. Sir, NBFCs
What a huge relief this is for him if you
Can you explain a little bit about NBFCs?
Your top picks in space because Shriram
Finances have been very good in the last few days.
It is seen moving. Ah, in this whole space
Which side NBFCs should you watch? Meaning
Normal trading or gold
On financing or some other section?
I think look at gold finance.
So we like both Mukut and Manpuram
But after Shriram Finance and then Bajaj
Finance: We think that all these companies
Stay focused because more is much bigger.
players and where the pay book size is large
Where they have good geographical reach
I think such NBFCs should be given priority
You should notice because somewhere
Somewhere this time in RBI policy also
There has been no change in interest rates
So I think this policy change has come
Large NBFCs should be looked at first.
Somewhere the market will see them first.
Their numbers will come after Q4.
The commentary that will come is also very important.
Will remain. So initially I think large cap
You should stick with NBFCs only.
Ok. And these rules have been simplified, sir.
If you could explain its meaning to us a little.
No, I think look at it clearly.
The funding requirement is a little
Structural process RBI uses it a little
Smothering out. somewhere that
This will simplify the process a bit and make it easier for larger
I think NBFCs should run their business
Will help increase it. how much on numbers
Sandeep, I think this will affect you.
Know from the management commentary after the above
Will work.
Ok. Ok. Well, apart from this, no sir, one
Trade deficit numbers also came yesterday.
FY26 numbers also came and March month
His number also came. So when March's turn came
Along with that, the number for the entire year also came.
of the financial year. As far as FY26 is concerned
If so, our trade deficit will increase.
119 billion has come. FY at $119 billion
This was the number in FY26 and in FY26 our
Imports have increased by around 6.5% and
Exports account for only around 5.25%
has increased and that is why our
There is a trade deficit for the entire FY26
It appears to be increasing. Although Sir Joe March
The numbers have come in March, if you
If you look at our exports,
have fallen by around 7.5% and imports
There has also been a decrease of around 6.5%. which is our
trade deficit is the trade deficit
AH decreased by 4.7% to $20.67 billion from $21.69 billion
It is seen reaching billions. So even if
Our numbers for the entire financial year are
It increased but the month of March was off.
Is. As far as trade deficit is concerned. in
Sir, how will the market react to the numbers today?
And what are these figures telling us?
No, look, I think the March number
We have noticed that there is definitely a slight slowdown in
has come and I think look at all these
The numbers are relevant as long as
The geopolitical situation is not clear. One
Once the geopolitical situation becomes clear
After that the markets give them a little more
I will give it seriously. I do not think that these
The number will spoil the mood of any market.
Look, there is still a lot of hope in the market.
Strong believes that very soon Iran and the US
The war will end and this is what the market is saying.
is giving a positive narrative. So I
numbers I think you might have a couple
Quarter or two quarters slightly soft
Will be seen but probably in the second half of F27
There will be improvement if we hopefully fight this war
It ends as quickly as possible.
Ok. Ok. One thing sir, I want to know about the results tomorrow
have come upon them after the market is closed
Let me focus. There are some numbers too, sir.
Coming today are Wipro, HDFC.
AMC is, HDFC is L, One is, VST
Industries, AOK Industries, Wari Renewal
And CRISIL numbers are about to come, sir.
So before the number sir any expectation or
Then if you guess some good number
They are running with any company
The big names are especially Wipro, HDFC
AMC or HDFC LJ One.
No, I think you should look at HDFC AMC.
We expect good numbers
Is. The numbers were quite good from January to March.
Will come because the SIPs were very strong.
The mutual fund market is doing very well.
It is growing. in the first quarter
The growth momentum is quite good. and Wipro
If we talk about it, then look at Wipro, the best
The big trigger will be those numbers, but
After that the buyback that they announced
How big will the buyback be?
Will it come at a price? Will it be tender or non-tendered?
It will be tender. I think the market
Hopefully, good premiums will be available.
There will be a buyback of Wipro. So these two
Stocks will likely be in the limelight today.
Yes, you talked about sectors, right?
Sir, IT was also one of the names in that. Now I
Remember what you said about auto capital goods auto
I talked about accessories and hotels. So
Sir what are your topics in IT?
Wipro or the giants TCS and Infosys
No, look at TCS Infosys, we think that
You should buy little by little from this level also.
Needed TCS numbers are much better than expected
Good, you have come. If we look at the fundamentals
So the cash flow of the company is the order book of the company.
It is very strong. Infosys also has a number
We think it will be quite good. HCL Tech
If anyone wants to buy one then a good one
There may be an option. But all these stocks
You need a minimum tenure of 12 to 15 months
Have to buy because movement is a bit slow
Will remain. But somewhere the market
It is expected that in the coming year,
The order book will increase. The rupee will also depreciate
If it goes then they will get some benefit from it too.
will get. But somehow I feel that
In the coming year, if hopefully AI
Any related company is more progressing
If it does, the market will also like it.
So somewhere I think these two or three
Focus on large caps. Wipro, we think
If the numbers are definitely good
So it will work fine after the results but
How will the numbers come, what is the commentary?
What will be the guidance, all these things
You will know after the results
Okay, so TCS Infosys and the third name you have
what did you say
I have said HCL Tech in large cap.
HCL Tech Okay, so you can invest in these stocks.
Focus and wait at least 12 to 15 months.
You should take a look at IT stocks.
You can also buy selectively and move ahead.
Are. Now, let us turn to something like this
of results, of such news stocks where
But updates came after the market closed yesterday.
Are.
First of all Sir ICICI LBARD in its numbers
I would like to discuss it with you. which of theirs
The profit is 5.25% on year-on-year basis, sir.
It grew to ₹547 crore. Gross
As far as premium is concerned, it is 17%
Grown around and operating profit
Look at the front, the numbers are even better.
There is an increase of around 31%. However, Sir, his
The underwriting losses are increasing further.
It is shown. ₹282 crore against ₹210 crore
has reached crores and a little combined
The ratio has also been seen coming down slightly.
Decreased from 102.5% to 1001.2%
But. What the ICICI LBA numbers are showing
Yes sir? And what is the complete general insurance today?
Space will be in focus after these numbers?
No, look, I think the numbers are
It's okay, it's in line. I think so
There is no surprise element. But
I think it's more than just a number.
It seems that a big rerating will happen immediately.
Not there. I think after the numbers
I think the market will expect that.
May the coming year be a good one
Because normally their March quarters
It is good enough for. Rough numbers
It's all right. But I think those who
Hold what is nearby. buying opportunities
I think if there's a little bit left in stock
Softness comes or lower level is found
Only then will the chances of buying increase.
Ok? So not now, if we meet a little below
Sure, you can go shopping. HDB
Financial Sir has been listed ever since
There hasn't been a major move since then.
Is. The numbers that came out yesterday are for the fourth quarter.
Sir, will they generate some enthusiasm because 40%
Their profits grew by more than Rs. ₹750
There was a profit of more than crores. And
Net Interest in IB See also in NI
There has been an increase of 21.6%. Based on these numbers
But sir, expect some rerating of the stock.
of
No, see this after a long time.
The numbers have arrived. So good luck to the market
It will be that for the first time after the IPO, the numbers are very high.
Okay, it has arrived. Definitely stock this morning
It will open well. But look, I think
that somewhere the market is giving it a little
Will take it consciously also. The market will expect
That this level should be sustained in future also because 40%
To maintain growth every quarter
Seems a bit difficult to do
Because the base is also big, so somewhere
I think there will be a slight increase.
But somewhere the stock will consolidate
And those who have it should hold on because
Roughly, if there is a growth of even 2025%
So I think that will be very beneficial for the markets.
If you like it then it is better to hold Age of Now
will remain
ok hold on tejas network sir their
The numbers were very good in the last quarter.
They were fantastic. Ah, that's great when I say that.
So I am talking about the last quarter.
I mean Q3. This is the number you got last time
The loss of the previous year is visible in front of us.
This is from the same quarter of the year i.e. Q4. So
Sir, their losses seem to be increasing further and if
I'm right, quarter by quarter, so it probably
have gone from profit to loss and their
If we look at the revenue, it has come down by 83% and
In fact, you can also see the Adda front.
From profit they have gone into loss after loss.
Sir, stability in TJS network numbers
Not there. There is a lot of fluctuation in this meaning
Ah, their numbers are quite very good. So
Sir, very good move in Tejas network
We have seen it being made. On the strength of these numbers
But why do you want to see what kind of reaction you have today?
Are you expecting?
Look at the numbers, I think this company
Just look at it quarter on quarter
It's difficult because it's quite long
Growth happens but the order book is good
I think the key points for 5G rollout
This is a very big vendor from the outside, so somewhere
Neither is your perspective long if it is a year and a half
Year same you know opportunity to invest in it
It will be made and I think that too, see when
You also said that there are unstable numbers, so such
In companies, I think the short term
Creating a view is a difficult thing, so
Only if we talk about the long term
Buying opportunities will be available at previous levels. But
In the short term, I think it's probably good.
There will be a jump once you see the numbers today.
After that some selling may be seen again.
We are fine. Okay, so let me give you some perspective.
We have to take it for the long term. This is the most
It is an important thing. If you like Tejas
If you want to create any position in the networks.
Well apart from this sir once you ji this gtpl
See also is. Ah, this is also a loss from profit.
I have come. There was a profit of Rs 10.6 crore.
He faced a loss of Rs 15 crore.
There is a jump in revenue. But amid
Look at the front, sir, there is a drop of 24.5% and
Margins that were around 12% are now 9%.
Have come under. After these numbers, sir
What kind of reaction are you expecting today?
No, this is a very bad number Sandeep.
I think maybe you'll need a down in the morning.
See the circuit. Because all the fronts
But the company showed very poor numbers. If
You look at revenue, IFTA, net loss.
Look, with such numbers the market definitely
Will not show enthusiasm. This is what I think
There is also a company conference call today. So
Company management on a conference call
What does the growth outlook of the stock say?
Whatever he does will also be important. But
Only after that I think it will be in stock.
Properly a directional trend will be seen.
In the morning session, I think it's below
It should open only.
Ok, good. Ok. Apart from this, Sir, once
Look at the delivery. Yesterday you delivered
You must have seen that a big block deal was done, sir.
In which Nexis Fund held 4 million shares or 53%
I have sold my stake. The price is 465 sir
On top of which this block deal for ₹186 crore
It has happened. The shares have been sold. Morgan in this
Stanley Hiddle Wise Mutual Fund
Goldman Sachs npon India Mutual Fund
and Vidian Asia Opportunity Fund 6-6
Bought one lakh shares. So sir this block deal
After this, what kind of move will you make in delivery now?
Are you expecting it today?
No, look, the numbers are enough in my opinion.
Good ones will come. After a long time this company
I am seeing a turnaround and logistics
There is a lot of activity in the space. So look at this
The mutual fund that has been sold
This could lead to some short-term weakness.
Can. But we are waiting for the numbers.
do. I think this is short term
I may feel a little pressure. Because
Normally, after such bulk bill, stock
I see a slight downward trend
Is. But in the medium to long term, we
The company's prospects seem quite promising.
It is positive.
Ok. OK, that's perfect. GMR Airport
Sir, their Q4 business updates came yesterday.
According to that, the numbers that came
Of the passenger traffic, about 1%
There is an edge around. He reported the number
It has been done for 32 million i.e. 3.2 crores
Of. Domestic traffic is 24.1 million and
International traffic shows 77 lakh
Kia in his business updates. Sir GMR
How do you fundamentally view this stock of Airports?
Seems like?
No, look, I think the airport.
Infrastructure is very important in India
Airports are important for aviation
As it is in India right now,
There is a need for more airports
There is need. If we talk about GMR Airport
So I think if your perspective
It is quite long term. If at least one and a half
He is years old. Someone here, here you invest
Stay tuned because the company still has debt.
It is quite big. Profitability still intact
In a way, you know I don't. But somewhere
Such an infrastructure player very quickly
No one can even replicate it. so me
It seems that if there is a perspective of one and a half to two years
Stay invested. In the short term, this
There will be a big upside after the numbers come out.
It seems like.
Ok, good. Ok. Once Sir, you and
Please give your view on pharma also.
Regarding the entire pharma space as well as pharma
The news came that they have a subsidiary
Sir Theranum Biologics
who introduced contract manufacturing
Operations which are the existing CMO operations of
The agreement was further expanded for him
Is. He worked with Muck Sharp and Dom
He is Singapore based and he has this with him.
Your CMO
He has a contract and further expands it.
Have done. It has been expanded. and Pharma
This is such good news, sir. Condition
At present, their buyback has also been announced.
Was.
Absolutely, good news and I think
The stock should open positively today. somewhere
Neither would the market expect its impact
over their earnings in the March quarter
No, but at least from the June quarter onwards.
And if we talk about buyback, I will get
It seems that somewhere in the market this is also
Hopefully, the buyback will also be good.
At an attractive price. So somewhere
There is definitely a positive bias in this. This too
It should open positively. We are like that sir
The buyback price arrived at in the previous buyback
The price is even higher. According to you sir
You can refer your clients to your members.
Do you recommend buyback in this?
Should shares be tendered?
Look, I think the buyback is not available.
Yes, but somewhere I feel that if
Some have a large quantity and some have a little
Offer a buyback. From that he definitely
There will be benefits in the near term.
And sir, what is your view regarding pharma?
In pharma, we feel that look at the big
There are companies like Sun Pharma, Lupin,
Torrent Pharma is a US related
Catering to markets, I find them there.
Looks like we're going to see a good increase
will get it because for a long time no US
FDI issue has not come. market growth
It is also quite good. So definitely these big ones
I think the companies here are the primary focus.
Should be.
Ok. Ok. So your take on large caps
There should be more focus. real estate space
What is your view on this? Sir, recently
The kind of decline we have seen at the moment.
However, the announcement of RBI policy
After that some hopes were made from the lower level
Recovery has also taken place. a brigade
There is news about Enterprises, Sir.
He has purchased 8.63 acres in East Bengaluru.
A joint development agreement for the land
Have done. JDA has been done. And so far this
Largest Integrated Residential
There is a township project for them. So
Brigade Enterprises is located in Abhi Purvankara.
Business updates came. Sir, on Monday his
We saw the reaction. Stocks Up Around 10%
I had gone. So Sir, the kind of decline that has occurred
There is value in real estate stocks right now
What is the situation in real estate as a pack?
There is a drop at the moment and what are your picks?
are from this entire sector
No, I think if you look at Mumbai
If you look at the market or Noida market
I think location specific is still
There is a very good demand. I think that
If we talk about Bombay Market
So there is Ob Reality which is a very good option.
Can. We also took Loda very positively.
looking at it because they have a very good
There is inventory. Prices in the market too
It has not fallen. If we talk about Delhi,
If we talk about Noida, Anant Raj is quite interesting for us.
I'm liking it. Even at the current level
Because they have very good positioning
Is. Somehow I think you
Purvankara Brigade is also present in Bor Market.
You can invest a little in companies.
Are. Provided your viewpoint is at least 12
to 15 months. Look at everything in real estate.
The decline had come and it has come. Back to the market now
Settling down and coming somewhere
The year will be very good for them. We are good
Is. So where do you find region specific?
Opportunities should be seen accordingly, Anantraj
In the Northern region or Delhi NCR
In the region and if you talk about Mumbai region
If you do, then take developers there or
Obro Realty These are some of the stocks where
You can see a very good trend.
Is. Apart from this, Sir, once you visit Rubicon
Also tell me about your research once.
View what is happening regarding this stock
Sir, this IPO came and after IPO, money
The level at which this IPO is being made
After it came, a very good trend was being created.
Just yesterday an update came regarding market closure.
Later he started the company named Arena Life Sciences.
has bought 85% of a company
Sir, this is a deal worth around ₹176 crores and
What happened with this deal, ah, that their
CNS is the formulation segment or CNS
i.e. Central Nervous System Formulation
Their entry into the market
It has been seen. Sir, you are grateful for Ruby research.
How positively do you see this thing?
No, enough, look, the company has done quite well.
Acquisition has been done and its impact is
It will definitely come on their numbers. I think
It is believed that the coming year will bring EPS for them.
It should be accretive because with this business
The company will get a lot of U-Know benefits. So
Definitely not only in today's session
The session should open well. Butt coming
Hopefully this unit will treat them positively in the session
Will contribute. So definitely anyone
Accumulate if you see a decline
But the outlook is medium to long term.
Ok. So buy on dips and
You can take a medium to long term view in this.
Take it with you. One sir you tell me Lakshya Powertech
What if you track this company, sir?
Tell me about it. to them with knowledge
Got an order yesterday for around ₹642 crore
and integrated services amounting to Rs.
For ONM for Operations and Maintenance
Sir, the assets of Ken are in Rajasthan.
For their Barmed assets
Sir, they have received this order worth ₹642 crores.
The stock is also reacting to target power.
Yes sir, on top of this in pre open it is 19%
Sir, this company is showing the surrounding jump.
If you track a little bit about it
Tell me how much value it has
What is this stock like fundamentally?
No, look, after a public issue.
He gave a very good performance and
This big order that has come is definitely
Their visibility will further increase revenue.
And I think the way it is now
The next year will be in FY27, I think
There will be a lot of growth because the
You will also see its impact this year.
I think I will find it somewhere
Let the stock cool down a bit and then
There will be buying opportunities but fundamentals
Looks pretty good from the point of view
I think if there's a little bit of stock consolidation
After the reaction you no longer react and correct yourself.
If it happens then one should understand the buying opportunity.
Ok? Ok. So in the fall, if you find this
If you get it then you should definitely buy it.
There should be opportunities. A must be found
Because the stock is very valuable
And the impact of the order received today
You should look at the stock on the positive side.
is getting it. A Sir GAV Infra GHV
infra if you track this sir
Received an order yesterday for ₹815 crore
Infratech Pvt Ltd Se Road
Construction and others in Maharashtra
For civil service For civil work
GHV Infra Project Sir its conversation
It is quite less. I think looking at their charts
It seems like the volume might have been lower.
will be. If you track this sir
So the value of the order is good. on stock
What should be done?
Look, those who have it should hold on.
But as you said, in this company
Liquidity is very low. So I would say that
In the market, those who basically need liquidity
is the primary focus. This is a little bit you know
Wait for liquidity to increase. But
Who are long term medium term investors
They definitely make a small investment in it.
Because normally we have seen that whenever
Some big positive fundamental news comes and
As fundamentals change, so does liquidity.
If it increases automatically then it is long term
Definitely the prospects are looking good.
Are.
Ok. Ok. Sir, you talked about hotel space.
that you will find Indian Hotels in the hotel space.
Feels quite good. Lemon tree or
Sami Hotel Sir. Sir, regarding Sami Hotels
Yesterday a news also came that they had one
Signed long term lease sublease agreement
Is. 162 room hotel in Noida
Sir, he signed this for the project.
Have done. One of their subsidiaries is Sami Sky.
Line Private Limited through which this
They signed a long-term agreement.
Is. How do you like Sami Hotels, sir?
In the hotel space?
Definitely not a long term hotel
Sami Hotels is quite good. Look at the numbers
Good ones will come. I think overall
The industry is also growing very well and
Somehow the market feels that
Hotels are one such sector in the domestic sector
where the growth momentum is still good
Is. If supply is limited then ARR which is room
Rentals are also quite positive. So
I think this acquisition is
Definitely earnings will be accretive but
Somewhere the perspective is a little medium term
I must keep it.
Ok, good. Ok. So medium term outlook
You keep it. But in the medium term, their
This can prove to be quite accretive. One
Sir, please give me your view on LIC.
As I told you yesterday, the market
Commentary at the beginning that 1:1 bonus
It has been announced Sir, whose impact we have seen
Looked at the positive side in the stock. 5% of
There was overall strength in LIC stock. Today
There is also an increase of around 1%. Sir, once upon a time
We have seen it above 1200 also. 850 K
Sir, how are you feeling about LIC around? And sir
Frankly speaking, I understand a little logic.
I did not understand what to do with giving bonus at this time.
Was there justification?
No, look, I think the logic is
I also did not understand but the public
equity share holders I remember this
I did IO for around ₹900 ₹950 and since then
These stocks don't make much money for retail investors.
If I haven't been able to make it, I think
This is good news for them because ultimately
Their cost will be slightly averaged out.
If it happens then at least for retail shareholders
There is good news for. This is good news. Me
I think maybe you know the management
I thought maybe you know retail a little bit.
Benefits should be given but still this logic
It does not sit because the public share is still
Holding Sandeep, you might also know that
Barely 2% is the maximum benefit
Only the Government of India will get it.
will get
It is a float of the same Sir.
That's what I mean it's a bit illogical but then
Still there is a government company and the government
You know how to understand decisions a little.
It is difficult but whatever happens, net net
Shareholders who have made a public issue
A little relief for those who have invested money in
It is reported that their cost is almost half.
Will be done.
We are absolutely okay, so share its benefits.
Holders will get it. Especially retail shares
to the holders who have invested in its public issue
I invested money and that money is still lying idle.
Is. If seen according to the issue price
So, we will have to see how the stock reacts.
He does it in today's session also. But in the meantime
You will see the markets in the pre-open.
Show me the bar Nifty. 150 points
Expected gap up opening with surrounding gains
It is expected to hit the Indian markets today.
Has been. With a lead of around 80 points
Ah it seemed that gift nifty indicator
doing. But the beginning is Nifty
If you look at the business I did today
So it has improved a lot as compared to what
We are waiting to see the trend in ah gift nifty
Were meeting. So if you look at it now
You will see the level around 24346.
We are open at the level of 24385. 24,231 this
We had our closing yesterday. So according to that
If we look at the numbers that have opened,
The better it is, the more we get the gift Nifty
Was indicating. But a good opening.
After this, there is some pressure from higher levels also.
It is visible. So we have 24385 only
Clocked. We crossed 24,300.
But it took some time to stay above 24,350.
Nifty is having to struggle further
You see, around 24,350, ah, Joe
Most of the time, he tries to spend with you
It will also be seen in Nifi. Sir once 24300 this
How big do you think the resistance was?
or how difficult it was to cross and
If we stay on top today, we won't tomorrow.
Was it possible or did it not happen last time?
found what we attempted because
There was a big resistance at 24303 so if this
The level has been crossed today sir, so what should you indicate?
Now let's see which new levels are opening up.
are coming to you
No, look, I think it might be
If FI buying were back to positive today
So crossing this level again is not a big deal.
There will be no problem.
But I think look at the market,
Yesterday you ran away and today you are saying that
150 points have opened. somewhere or the other
There will be some consolidation in the market. somewhere
The market is also expecting this somewhere.
that the things that Mr. Trump is saying right now
They will stick it on top of that. if anyone
If a negative surprise comes, then definitely this
It is a bit difficult to cross the next level.
will be. So I would say a little
[sound of clearing throat] Very profitable.
Recovery will also come because of yesterday's big gains.
After doing 150 points today, a little bit
Selling may also come. So a little bit of a wet end
Watch it. It doesn't seem so soon today
This level should be crossed immediately during the session
Can.
We are fine. Your take on Bank Nifty
Tell me once sir. Tomorrow we will be around 56300
Were closed. 5657 means 350 points
There was a gap up in Bank Nifty today as well.
And still you see the day high around 5650
Nifty Bank trading around
You can clearly see what he's trying to be.
Will come. So sir as compared to Nifty what
Bank Nifty may look better to you.
Used to be? PSU banks or private
How do you calculate the contribution of both banks?
Let's see? Sir, in anticipation of inflation
We have also seen the numbers. RBI's
We have policy and now war too.
Crude stable around 95 after stopping
It seems to be happening. of this entire scenario
In the meantime, Sir, your views on banking stocks
What is a view?
No, our view on banking is positive.
Look, I think banking is
Very reasonable quarter to quarter
Will show. However, look at the Treasury side.
A little bit of caution in the market right now
That maybe banks are showing treasury losses
Can. But I don't think that's the
There will be some big you know panic. My thoughts
Core business of banks is doing very well since
Is. And there I think the government
There are banks like SB, Canara Bank,
Bank of Boudha is private in U know
ICICI Bank is there. in small public sector banks
Bank of Maharashtra. over these banks
Focus. I think credit growth
Slowly slowly coming into double digits.
Obviously in the coming year, the kind of
Government has capex, private
Capex is somewhere the market expectation
It is believed that if the economy does well
It grows and if the auto sector does well
If volume growth is seen then for banks
You will get good business. So we are positive but
Definitely take a little bit of a medium term view.
It is necessary here.
Okay, fine. Ok. We also visited the market
Had a conversation. Now We Move On To Hot Stocks
Towards. Focus on such stocks
Where a lot of action is taking place and your
Trying to answer the questions
Are.
Like yesterday, sir, today also all the sector indices
Positive means business with strength
Are seen doing it. And today's this
There is speed, if someone is leading it
Sector so that's reality defense media
Capital Market Metal Tourism and Aftermath
The name of IT comes up. Some IT stocks
But there are some sirs who move very well.
Have been. And even in that, there are no giants who are in mid
Sir, those are stocks from the IT space.
Seems to be more active. I
I want to put some names before you. in that
You should look at the Sonata software. E Clerk
See the service, you see the first source in it
You can see the intellect here, this is
All mid-cap and small-cap IT space
There are stocks, sir, at least three-quarters of them.
The upmove of up to 9% is worth watching.
Sir, you are getting more in mid cap IT.
Is there any value or is it something beat and down?
Names that have great value
No, look, I think there are two here.
There are three stocks that we like very much like
KPIT is coffers, it is persistent but
I would say, let the numbers come.
Because the market feels like
If large cap IT has run then definitely
Possibility of good growth in IT as well
Is. Definitely after the numbers come, a little more
Clarity will come. But it seems that somewhere
Neither anywhere else, if here also if positive
If we look at the trend numbers, then this increase
You can see it with a little bit of love
The players in the market are doing
Are. So definitely medium to long term
The prospects are good for
When the numbers come, then there will be some clarity.
Will come. So I think there's no hurry
Don't do it because see if one or two companies
If I get a negative surprise, it
The growth you get in a small cap IT company
She seems to be stopping for a while.
Can. So wait a little before investing.
Let the Q4 numbers come. Commentary coming
Give it. After that a clarity is better
Will get it.
Ok? So the first thing you should do for new investment
So what about Q4 results and management's
The commentary is coming, you wait for it.
Take it because to a large extent this new thing is
The financial year has started on 27th, how is it
What kind of scenario will be painted when orders come
Your understanding of what the outlook is like
It will happen but in the mid-C IT space, Sir,
KPIT Tech Course and Persistent
These are their favorite stocks. So IT stocks
Sir, little pieces for investment in
I should not invest even 10 paise each, eh?
Then wait a full minute and only then
Create a position.
Yes, you can apply it also. Look who is higher risk
There are investors who are a little
Take a little position in bits and pieces
Can. But whenever you buy any stock
If you buy in an uptrend then
You already know that you are a little late.
So I think you buy 202%.
This will probably be fine for traders. But
For investors, I think it's important to stay
No problem because right now the numbers
Come back out in roughly a week.
They are the same ones. So there's no long wait.
Is.
Ok? So there is not much time. you want
20% if you are a high-risk investor
You can invest the money now. ₹20 out of ₹100
Apply it now. The rest is a little weight of numbers.
Do it or you will get the chance gradually.
So keep adding to these. Giants
I told you sir about HCL Tech,
Infosys and TCS and MidC in the IT space
KPIT Tech, Co. and Persistent These Few
There are stocks that Sir likes very much
Is. Brigade Enterprise Sir, I request you
He was also talking about the joint
Has a development agreement been made?
Look at the impact of this 4.5% with one lakh shares.
Trading strongly around
It is visible. Sir at Brigade Enterprises
It is already in position if taken in the bottom
It has happened. Should you book profit or else
Wait now and there is upside.
No, I think it would be better to wait.
Look at the impact of this development.
See you in the coming quarters
It will be available and fundamentally the company is very good.
Is. Quite prominent in Bore Market
Is a player. So I think those who have absolutely
The short term view is that they can leave.
But those who have at least 6-12 months
The time frame is definitely here.
Will remain invested.
Ok. One for me Sir Railte and Railway
Please give your view on stocks also. Yesterday I
I told you RT just received an order.
From RBNL. Its impact on the stock is estimated at 18%.
Shown as a boom. See even today 4 4.5%
strength around and the best thing that
Isn't it sir, that is volume. You still look at
In the 4-4.5% move you see
Volume should be more than 6 million shares
Already happened. Sir, is it correct to assume that
Some institutional buying is taking place in the Railways.
Stocks too because there is a lot of beat
And down names are this value is quite good
Is. If you also agree with this
Yes sir. Some stocks you like
From Railway Age a Pack?
No, look, I think the railway sector
Just two days ago, the news came that
The government has spent approximately Rs 1,53,000 crore.
The budget plan has been approved. So definitely
Look, the company which makes wagons, which runs on railways
It definitely creates infrastructure.
They will get benefits. Talking about wagon companies
So we still have Jupiter Wagen, Tax
Maco, TG I like this a lot. long term
Their business model is very strong.
Because look at the few companies in India
Makes wagons. As for the real thing,
We think this would also be a good option.
Can. RITES, a consultancy player
He also does a great job for the railway sector.
Is. Somehow I feel that the railway
I definitely have to have some patience and wait.
It is necessary because the way the government
She is spending money, its effect is definitely there.
Will come. In RT, you saw that big orders
It has come and Railte definitely we feel that
If someone wants to buy at a lower level then
Little by little, here also through an SIP
Buy from a point of view because somewhere
Somewhere the volumes are showing that somewhere
There is good institutional buying in this
Is.
Sir, you are saying that we are on Railway as a pack.
That we should wait a little now.
No, you can also invest a little.
But only those investors should invest here.
Whose minimum age is 15 months
There is a view. Because we have seen that the upper
These stocks are quite beaten down from their levels, they have fallen
Are. So not for traders but investors
a little bit for definitely here you have a
You can buy it in small pieces
Are.
Ok. Not for traders but for investors
There is a chance for it. If your long term view
So sir, all these stocks are good.
You took names. RT JWL Texmao Rail TG
Rides
No, of course, look at the good positional in TG.
A view can be created. Then there's the Jupiter Wagon.
Is. Texmao also looks quite attractive.
So somewhere I think a basket
Make it and these in two-three stocks
You can deposit a little bit of money.
We are fine. Ok. So not for traders
For long term investors
Good money can be made in railway stocks
And some names have been mentioned to you, at least some of which
Less if you take a 12 to 15 month view
If you go ahead, you can make good money. So
There is some value in these stocks
Institutional buying interest is also expected
Are getting. with significant volumes
Some buying interest is coming in these so you
Selectively and gradually take a long-term view
You can pick up railway stocks from here. Name
Placed before you by Avinash Sir
From. Well Sir, if we look at the infrastructure, today we
Looking at Sir Fcus Infra Day 2
When there is a lot of strength in the stock
Has been. It is still up 4.5% today. So some infra
There are some such counters in space too, sir.
In which the value is quite good.
Look, I think construction companies
Talking about it, NCC is looking good.
If we talk about pure infra, I
I think L&T is also quite good. His
Later, if we talk about capital goods, you know
I would say the action construction is also quite
Is good. So I think look at the numbers.
Let it come, but the market has to come somewhere
It is expected that infra-specific
The sector which is purely capital goods
I mean capital goods companies
There might be a good trend there.
Because corporate capex is increasing and
Somewhere I think the companies that
The numbers for these are sitting in good order.
If they come out quite good then I think it's okay to wait.
It will remain but definitely the trend will be positive.
such to me
Okay, please show me ICICI LBAT once.
After the LBA results, you will see a slight
It will be seen trading with a decline.
It opened higher at ₹1867 with a slight gain.
Also strengthened by 1/2% to ₹1892
Went but could not survive at higher levels
And along with this, you should see New India.
Insurance is a company in this space. one day
Very good move sir New India
in insurance and from then on you see
New India Insurance for two consecutive days
There is also a significant decline in
Has been. Sir, regarding this entire space, General
This ICC LBA regarding the insurance space
What are the views after the numbers have come?
Should it be made?
Look, as I told you, the numbers
Those who have come in March, I think there is hope
came in slightly lower because it was due to growth
The market is not giving any immediate rerate to this stock.
I won't do it, but I think I'll come.
The coming year may be good for them.
There were definitely a lot of challenges in the market.
had become competitive which have a long duration
This sector has a one and a half to two year outlook.
Stay in because in the short term it seems
No, there will be a big increase here, we will be fine.
yes ok it is perfect apart from this sir i want a
Please give your view on sugar stocks.
If seen fundamentally, whenever crude
Prices increased, sir. In this war, we saw that
Even in this entire Chinese space
Looks like a very good activity
Because the ethanol play is active
It happens. If we look at it sentiment wise
We have seen very good buying interest in these.
It was seen being made. Those who have also reached lower levels
But our experts have
The recommendation given has been taken by word of mouth.
A lot of money has been made there. Now Sir
How to deal with sugar or sugar stocks
Should there be a view of? who have low levels
I have taken it, I should sell it and make a profit.
Should recovery be done or is there still a chance?
Are. What can be purchased is some selective
To sugar stocks?
No, look at the integrated players.
Like Rampur has become Balrampur, Chinese have become
If I went there, I think you would have a
One should have a good positive view. he too
Pay a little dip because stocks
have run away from the lower levels and
The government's proposal is that ethanol
Blending has increased from 20 to 21%, its effect
Definitely it will come little by little and if you assume
Let crude go back and level up
Pay goes back to these stocks
I'll see you back for a little rally.
Will get it. So in the near term view, more
And less stocks will consolidate but
In the medium to long term, I think
If you get opportunities here,
You should add it at the level.
Ok? If you meet at lower levels then definitely
Should be added. Sir Metal Age carrying a pack
Give your view. When you looked at some sectors
I had talked about auto, capital in the beginning,
Goods, Hotel, Power, Auto & SL in IT
And you also mentioned metal. Tomorrow in Metal
We saw Halcoc Sir reach an all-time high
Went. Aluminum prices have risen in this way
Have been. NALCO is also doing well. 2.5%
It's above. It would have been a good move in Vedanta too.
It seems to have happened. GPIL Ek and Power Esi
Space company is where we are looking
There is an upmove of 1.5%. In this entire space, sir.
What are your topics? In the metal space
Should you stay in a copper space longer?
Pick up aluminum stocks or
Then should we focus more on steel?
No, I think that's First Steel,
Is it Tata Steel or after that is Halco,
Vedta. I think in such stocks
Definitely the movement will be positive because
I think the March quarter numbers.
They will be very good and overall global
Metal prices are also rising in the markets
Are. So somehow I think that
You will see a good bullish environment in the metal sector.
It will be seen and this is probably the market too.
It is showing. So two or three stocks that I
Let's say if anyone here is a little bit moderate
Will there be a correction or will it go a little higher?
If you are a trader with a risk appetite, then a little
Build a position because numbers matter to me.
will become much stronger than that, after that the growth
Commentary will come after the results and that too from me.
The market will be closely monitored.
So you said sir Tata Steel HCO third name
What did you take from the metal space?
I have spoken Danta
The data is fine, keep an eye on these stocks.
What should be the viewpoint in this, Sir?
How many views should one take to invest at least
do
No, I think at least six or eight.
Keep an eye on the month because the metal cycle
Now getting back positive after a long time
And hopefully I think that this
The US-Iran war has begun, plus the
The price movement in metals is due to
It seems that aluminium and ferrous metals
It will run well and you will get huge benefits from it.
Companies will get what they deserve Hindalco
It is Tata Steel, so first of all this large
Focus on companies
Okay, one last question for you, sir, before that.
Let me take leave of you. One on our Facebook
Our audience is
Midmoy Jana ji. They are saying that Sir
Which stock doubled in the recent 2 months?
Will you give profit? I want to invest
Of ₹10,000. Basically these sir such stocks
Want to know where to go with the numbers?
Have a positive view or good numbers
are supposed to. So if you want to invest ₹10,000
In this anticipation in the market
Good
10,000 ok yes I am asking for 10,000 only
This amount is not that big. So where
The numbers may be good. like these
If before the results in anticipation
Sir, someone has to earn money only in such stocks.
I am asking you where you got good marks.
And invest the money in advance.
No, I think there are very few like this.
Stocks are there but still government banks
Bank of Maharashtra is a good option.
It is a very reasonable price. Numbers me
Looks like they will be quite good. approximately 6000
There will be a profit of crores this year.
So it seems that definitely numbers
Later, a small uptrend may occur and
He has 10,000. So in my opinion this
You can choose Bank of Maharashtra. One
Reasonable risk reward. Plus you know
Invest at the level at which the share price is
There's a little you know to do
potential was created
We are okay, so focus on PSU banks.
Do it specially Bank of Maharashtra one two
Name and you had taken it sir which you got from PSU
Overall choice in banks
No, look, Canara Bank is also very good.
Bank of Boudha is also good, SB is also good
Yes, but I think look, when you have
It's only 10,000, so I think it's more.
If there is no space left for allocation then I
I would say take what you like.
But Bank of Maharashtra is a good risk
The bed can be made because you know 65 or 68 or
I think close to 6970 is and this
From the level I think if the numbers are good
If you come then there is a good risk near it
Can be made in term. Look at the short term
It is very difficult in trade to tell how much
The stock will move because we will see it now.
that the stock fell after the results were announced
goes. So keep that in mind as well
The results are never perfect
If good results come then the stock will move. a little
Shares start moving even before the results. So
Keep in mind that purely numbers
You Know Will Not Be the Right
Strategy.
Okay, fine. Thank you very much sir. Thank you
You so much please spend your precious time with us today
To share. a lot of stocks
There has been discussion and debate regarding this. Enough
We have discussed all the sectors. Sir
Any disclaimer?
Watch Sandeep, whatever stocks we have on your show
Talked about it. Our clients may
We told the same stocks but personal
The position is nothing like that.
Well, thank you very much sir. thank you so
Mach. Precious time to share and wish you
A very good day sir.
Let another special guest join us now.
Have been. Join us at BN Securities
Rachit Khandelwal, Head of Research,
are attending the program. Very
You are welcome sir. The tie disappeared red
Of color. Is this the biggest sign?
Very good morning sir. [Laughter]
Hello to you sir. Hello to all the viewers.
Sir, the tie also disappeared because
Practically you see one thing in the way
We can see the whole situation unfolding and
Sudden switch a which was seen followed by a which
If the market is in momentum then tie
Nifty levels are better than indications
See now, but yes, I will definitely say one thing.
Sir that a little bit in the way the crude is still
A conscious approach is maintaining us
Should not be left and cease fire must be observed
It is visible now. for a long time
There is a sense of peace and it feels good.
It seems that finally a little settlement has taken place.
headed towards. Abhi US India Trade
There is no sign of a deal anywhere.
It is being seen happening somewhere. So
The situation seems a little relaxed now.
So back to geopolitics and
Paying attention to Nifty levels. And
Clear case indication sideways movement to
It is of positive bias only. So today I said
Let's leave it.
I will not leave you but Sir I
I will ask you that question again. 22182
Is it a bottom or is it a swing low?
Sir, if I comment on this now, it will be very
You will wonder what kind of things they are talking about. But
I still can't accept that.
which is creating the entire situation and in fact a
One more thing we have to see, sir, is that the market is
We may still see it sustaining
Because the numbers that are coming so far are
I seem relatively fine but the pain point is
Just a little bit to say what's over
It will be difficult because the numbers that will come now
I mean, just look at our OMC numbers right now.
The rest of March is his pain point.
is and still is the way crude is maintained
It is putting some pressure on you there too.
can still be seen and
running the card
You
Please
Sir is saying something
No no sorry please continue sir
No sir, no sound
No, sorry sir, sorry, please continue.
Please
no good okay and still the way
After the war is over, how will
Strait of Amers reacts. What
The gas supply is restored in this manner.
So we have definitely seen a bounce back. But
How does Going Forward Energy affect our
She lives in the situation. And this one that we
have seen the typical pain period that we are currently
A little bit of that in this quarter too
Will see the reflection. His numbers coming up
We will see it and as long as Mr. Trump is there
Will everything remain the same?
We will have to watch a little bit because right now during the week
He also said this in the beginning
Tha after I'm done with Iran Cuba and
other places are in radar to
Is the 2200 level the bottom? Tell me now.
It is difficult
Sir, he is a hardworking man, something or the other is on his radar
I always stick to my timetable
Is the schedule complete?
Yes, I mean it fits faster, you see.
Inspired from here back here in the US
There will be talk about India trade deal. I hey
Brother, it's been a year since you did the trade deal.
Nothing is happening while we're talking
Pe and a little bit lighter than Iran because I was a
Let me tell you something sir, as much as we can
Hearing the statement that China will let you know
Chinese leaders will give me a big fat hug and
All these things are coming from them.
Is. No confirmation from China
It is coming. How will the second round of talks take place?
There is going to be a lot of damage to Iran.
There is not much clarity coming. it is
Just a bounce back that we are seeing and
It's time for respite. So we just have to
Play with the levels. And still what is this
They say we are out of the goods. Tell
It is difficult, sir. Trump being Trump anytime
Can do anything.
Okay then please tell me the levels sir. 24,350 K
We are above. Until yesterday it seemed like
Crossing 24,300 is a bit difficult.
He was proving to be a wall. But today the
This way we decisively crossed 24,300.
I am sitting here doing it. Now according to you sir
Levels are important then I am the audience
Let me move on to the questions. Sir 2450 K
Up till we are maintaining 2450050
We can see levels up to this level.
There is little supply there.
It can be because the off flow is so much when
As we go up, we make profits at higher levels.
Taking becomes inevitable. And if we
Talk about Bank Nifty Bank Nifty too
You will see till it stays above 55800 levels
He is maintaining it. 56,900,
57,300 are the levels we are focusing on.
Can do.
56,900
and 57,300
Yes.
Ok. And in Nifty you have upside at 24,550
Bid as long as we are above 2450.
Yes yes sir.
Ok. Ok. So this level is in front of us.
Went. Keep these levels in mind.
Sir, usually you used to complain and call.
They don't give, they don't call. Enough you will believe
Not on Thursday when I was last with you
I went after doing the show and then from Friday onwards
I mean it doesn't mean you
We were able to meet but start making calls.
I had given it to you just now, Sir, because it had been so long.
Doing shows with you after the break
PGEL can focus on this and do well
It seems at these levels, at 543, 544 levels
It's going well at these levels.
There was a good movement yesterday as well, bye tomorrow
The freezer was also done. 568 588 levels
which can be seen. But One Thing
Is for sure and which is varied. Stop
Don't forget the loss. with a stop loss of 528
Also, focus can be given on this.
568 is the second target, sir. The first 553
No no sir. 568 is the first target. 588
There is another target.
588 Okay. Ok. So the stop loss is 528.
568 588 These are your targets. to PGL
Yesterday we also saw a move of 10%.
We even had a buyer freeze. 545 K
I told you around here that it is up to ₹588.
You may see the stock going away. So sir
This is excitement till 2450. This PGL of yours
Got on the buying list or something
Stocks that appear on your shopping list
Started. No sir, one thing is clear, I mean look.
When the times of respite are received
Trading can be done only with that and
I will still say one thing Sir Pain Point
Is it over? It's too early to
Will we see the down side again?
Yes, that's why I will reinstate it.
Focusing very strongly on stop losses
Do it and don't forget that the last 40 days
Which we have told how many pens, how much tension
And spent in stress. As soon as the stop
Loss triggers should come out of these trading calls
Should go. This is what I'm saying to you too
Was. Sir, in the last few days when you talked
I was telling you that when
Is there a bounce back or is there a pullback?
If there is any response or if any response is coming then
Respite to Why Not Play That Bounce.
remember when
Sir, of course, you did the grill and
The advantage that was there spread everywhere else.
It kept happening.
I was just highlighting sir that the one who
Ambala Ma'am was associated at that time, she was saying
That's a bounce back of 1.5 to 3%. I
I wanted to tell you the same thing. I to you
I am not saying that you should change your view.
Give it. I'm not saying people are buying you beer.
They are saying. why are you being slow
Are. That is the view point. I have your view
I have always heard the point completely sir. I to you
This has been said somewhere. But one thing I
I also requested you that when a little bit
Respite comes when there's a bounce back
So why not trade in that a little?
A view should be created. That's why I told you
asked that the excitement is up to 24,550 as far as
If you are looking at the upside then it is the same thing
There is one more thing with him sir if
Let's assume that all these things are through
If it goes then Nifty will also go above 24500.
caste
That's fine sir 24550 is still visible if
Things are good if all goes well then
If 24550 is also crossed then it will be a new all time
It will also look high
[nasal sound] like situation
There is nothing like that in panning out.
Sir, let me take some questions from the audience.
I'm walking and some stock if in front of me
I will see that those who are very active are me
I will ask you before leaving. uh good at it
First tell me one Paras defense.
Sir, the level is 768, it is 2.5% up. not one tomorrow
Sir, the news came that he did not get an order.
Is. Let me tell you what happened. yesterday 7 8%
There was a move of around . Tomorrow at Paras Defence
The news was like this, sir, that these
They have signed an agreement.
Star is a US company owned by North Star.
Named To Supply and Support North Star
Products for Indian Armed Forces
Sir, this North Star will supply to US
And that in fact to the Indian Armed Forces
We will supply our own products.
So they supply some things to the US company.
will do and that in turn will later assemble
or using them
We will give those things to the Indian Armed Forces.
Sir, we have seen the impact of this in Paras Defence.
Saw it yesterday also. This is for adjustment sir
Now this level of ₹768 is at these levels
But how do you feel about this stock?
Sir, look at some fresh buying.
It seems dicey because yes this news
It is positive but this news in numbers
It will take some time to reflect and
In the defense space, Paras Defense is one such
If the price to book value is taken
If you see, it is trading at nine times.
Is. This momentum would have continued further.
It can definitely be seen what happened. I mean I
I will not say that the matter is over Nana
No, you may see further upmove.
Is. Running on 768 levels. Move to 769
Used to be. 784 and above
So it can go up to 80 levels also. But
The risk reward is therefore not favourable
Because the support is a little below it.
You will see this support taking you directly
At 664 levels. If this comes from somewhere
Turns on correction. So those who have
Maintain it now. But Fresh Buying
There is not a little advice.
So the stop loss is also 664 for those who
Holding on. Yes because you lower
We are keeping it from the level itself, right?
Is. So it can go up to 784 810. whose
If you have it, hold it till these levels. 664
That should be your stop loss. Don't buy new
Do it. Risk reward is good or favorable
Not there. Listen carefully. The levels you
We will move as per what is being told.
Neither will be of much benefit to you.
There is momentum in the stock. further upside for the stock
Can take it away. But don't worry about it.
This is the word for you regarding new purchases.
Off caution seems to be coming at the moment. Sir
Some questions
Sir, let me give you one more stock today.
I will give it on call. Ashapura
This company used to be called min. Now
This company has become Ashapura Mint Limited.
and 56869
It is running on levels. You can focus on this
Are. The way it's positioned is 584 and
If it sustains above 584 then 640 levels
Can show you up to. So 584 is the first
Target 640 will be the second target and stop
Stop loss is always necessary from loss edge.
Stop loss will be Rs 516. Ok? little by little
If I keep talking, will sir keep coming? [Laughter]
Sir, I am trying. Look at what you did that day
The thing I said was very important and after that
in fact same de nahi i was there for a
Event means evening I was out with some
Of my friends. So they also were cribbing
What about it brother, what are you doing? So much
Why are you sitting quietly? something or the other
Keep doing it. So I said okay.
Let's begin with it. So the same things are going on
Yes sir. Ok. It's perfect. some of our
Sir, we are friends who are our audience. Their
I am putting the question before you.
Aakarshan Kumar ji sir, his is the first question. These new
Join us as a member.
You are very welcome. Sir, he has one
One is Crumton and the other is Ionx Wind. He
I have taken futures. No Sir Price
Told at what price it was entered. But
Want your opinion.
Look, let us take it first. Sir, his
What are the stocks? One is Inox Wind
Second order.
The second is Kraton.
Let's talk about IOX Vent first.
Are. Running on 93 levels. One for these
It becomes a very important thing that this off
Flos is trading. A closing of 88
Basically they will have to keep stop loss. That
Momentum is building you up in the best way
First 98 and then sustains above 98
Can show levels up to. at a higher level
Book the position but stop loss again
Will reactate has necessary. The ordering also depends on its
Maintaining above 50 day moving average
Is. You can go into this with a stop loss of 244
Maintain your position. The first level which
It looks like it's 262 and above 262.
Sustain movement up to 274 levels
Can take it away. Again stop loss too
It is important.
Ok. Now when it comes to stop loss
Sir, I was reading the question of one Shankar Singh ji.
saying that uh I had AG double eye yesterday
AGI Infra was bought by Anshul
Stop loss at ₹374 from Zee's Telegram
Placed a trade and placed a stop loss at ₹339. Say
I'm afraid it ate my stop loss and
Then he came back to the same place. what big two
Traders eat our stop loss?
[Laughter]
No no, look, there is a clear case that means
Sir, this has become too much, understand that
One, no trades means now a randomly from you
Let me share a view point. Sir I came
Received a phone call and this person was
from northern part of India and he was
Very curious in discussing things and all
Things. He asked me a question
That seemed so alarming to me. You Spoke
You saw this in Ola Electric for Rs 5.15
Share work should be done. Work done for 5.25 crore shares.
Was. I said yes, it definitely happened. So
In this we can deal for 20 lakh shares.
Are. I said one go said yes here
You have to understand that algo is now so
It has become more important that if you
If you want to accept bulk orders then you
Please use the algo. the way in which
We used to trade in primitive style
Pay that you killed this quantity and did this
I gave it, I did it. it doesn't work like
That. If Ago has trapped you.
If the algo senses that you have
A trading position has been taken. It could be where
But right now these are our viewers who
Took position and other people also took that position at the same time.
Position should be taken at the level and stop loss
Must have placed it. Ago sensed it
I assumed that from here if I trigger the stop loss
I get it done. I can make this much of money. Ago
Triggered that stop loss and exited
I did it. I would not say that you
Do not place a stop loss. Understand stop loss and
Check it and place a stop loss.
instead, if practically possible for you
And if you can see in front of the screen
Because if you are trading
It's a variant that you can see a little bit on the screen.
Give yourself time to see the market conditions
After seeing this, move the stop loss up or down a couple of times and
Manage your position that way
Just for the Sec: Stop Loss Triggered Multiple Times
and then the stock starts moving back up.
Is. So the number of stop losses I place
Sir, you must have always noticed one thing that I
I say closing basis intraday levels
But definitely do that movement in that manner once.
You can, but even if it is on a closing basis
If you sustain it then yes selling pressure
has become dominant, so usually all our
Stop losses are closing basis.
Ok. It is perfect sir. some name is not this
Throughout the war I will give you a little
Don't take it otherwise sir, I am saying this because
I am hoping you have forgotten me, but I remember your
Good stocks are recommended
No, those who say about you that you are like me
Will be like a child. I so recommend
I have done it. I miss NLC India
Went. Sir, everything is going quite well today.
GMDC, NLC India, all these are rare
Stories related to meaning are there now.
It appears to be active. Sir GMDC
And please give your opinion on NLC India.
Sir, look NLC India, very good start.
I feel it since and I still feel it and I
I understand the movement it is making this time.
And you will see this in this week sir
Good in some trading sessions
There has been a volume build up. slightly to you
Supply can be seen. to 9094
As soon as it breaches the levels then you
Now it prepares for a good upside
It is showing what happened. Infact if its
If you look at chartal patterns
Practically this is equivalent to 10 years of age.
Let's come up with a level. those levels
294 296
Breach will now prepare it for you
324 and after 324, 348 levels which
Maintain the pass position. But there is also a
I will tell you the thing. Like speaking for everything
Have been. Stop loss will be called for this also.
It is necessary. Stop loss is a little below but
It becomes very important. 252 will have a stop
Loss. And along with this you can also buy GMDC.
See, in recent times it has done well
The momentum is ours. 52 week high
Trading at levels. This is also your
Breaching multi-year highs. Till the
Time it is maintaining comfortably above 574
Levels. You feel very comfortable 672
Getting ready for the end of 724 levels
Can be seen.
724 ok. Ok. Manmohan ji is saying sir
that I have SSWL steel tip
Wheels has 1500 shares at ₹214 and
Reliance Industries has 500 shares
13354 at the rate of ₹1354. I hold these
Should I do it or sell it?
Look, Reliance is not suitable for sale.
I mean, for Reliance, I want to tell you one thing.
I will speak. Quantity you consume a little at a time
I have taken C Heavy. But Reliance on God
Neither speciality nor God became special and that means that one
It is a matter of if you get that thing.
It seems that if Mr. Trump comes
Then you should pay less on Reliance Industries
You will get to average at the level. But no
I don't think you have anyone on this yet.
Action should be taken. Maintain the position now.
Steel SIP Wheels LED You can buy these
What is the price sir?
214 is currently trading at your buying price
Is. There is nothing for you to worry about in this
Not there. In this space, we look at a
You are seeing the momentum. In this
There was just one small problem that the last
Their numbers from the time were reported in that
He had given a little degrowth and that
Somewhere you have to calculate the price volume
You might have even seen it. Up to 1196 levels
As long as it is maintaining 228 levels
Very comfortable. And if you put it on medium
If we take the term approach then it is 248
It can also be seen going up to levels.
Sunita Chaturvedi ji is saying that sir
Sharda Energy is available with me at Rs 551.
And Finlex cable at the rate of Rs 921 for one year
Can you hold them, what is their target?
Will it be theirs?
Look, let's take Sharda Energy first. 591
running on. It is in good momentum. And
If you look at it fundamentally, I have no
The problem is not visible. just a little bit
Weakness was visible in the results that came.
But that should not be a problem. If you are a
If you hold it for a year, then very
Comfortably you 668 67
Can display up to 724 levels. and my
Hold it comfortably as per the requirement. a if something
It also gets bad, like suppose whatever we say
I am seeing that situation coming
then you have a little pen point
Can be seen. But at the very face
of it the way this position is 524
I can't see below the levels yet.
Am. So hold it comfortably. below it
If goes back by the bad news in the
There will be some problem in the market. Now this
You play it comfortably. Phenolics Cables
You also see the way the momentum is now
It is showing. Off flow well tread
He seems to be doing it. 200 Day 50 Day Moving Average
Maintaining above average. Absolutely
You should continue your respective positions. If
If you continue, you will reach levels up to 968.
You may get to see it. and in the
Let me tell you one thing that a stop loss
You must definitely tie it. If you find this for 842
If you see closing below, you
Be sure to place a stop loss because then
This odds can also reach up to 700 levels.
Ok. What are you saying at Vimta Lab?
Sir? Dilip Kumar ji is saying 464
There was also a breakout in this. Now they have
I don't know whether it is there or not but technically it is
There has been a breakout of 464.
Standing at 468, sir.
Look at this jis
Situation [nasal sound]
I'm talking about this breakout many times.
We think so, but it means more than that.
Breakout is very comfortable to play
I don't think so, but yes, I am comfortable with it right now.
The thing is that its 50 day moving average
Yes, he is at 456. on top of that as long as the maintain
Showing you up to 524 levels
Can. If your position is 456
Maintain with levels. If there is no
Well then. Anytime above these prices
Below you can see a little stop loss of 456
You can play for 524 levels with
Are.
Ok. A grow sell or hold Dilip Kumar
Yes, I am asking. The growth has doubled.
IPOs with almost 10% discount from their issue price
Standing at its high and targeting ₹235
Was. The report that came out yesterday, I think Morgan
Stanley's report, which he
You initiated the coverage of Sir Gro.
view
Sir, I am scared and very clearly
I say I am scared 17.5 times the price to
Book Value of a Stock Broking Firm 82
Everything is running at KPE multiple
ok i agree it is one of the
Biggest retail stock broking firm
accepted this also
But your revenue doesn't justify it.
Valuations are low, meaning I'll see what I'm talking about.
Not even comment if you have it I
I would say with my discretion and stop loss
Please play the position. I like this stock
I don't understand. If we talk about buying
Sometimes it will come at lower levels, sometimes it will correct
I will do it when I go. And sir, it's not like that.
We didn't see. You can check out Zomato.
swig look, Ola EIC look, ah two
A very grade extent somewhat metal
There were also stocks for which we saw higher levels
But I said that I don't understand.
And then what happens is that retail
Then you get trapped sir and you play stop loss.
I couldn't do it, I couldn't do it, it's not good for me
Stocks with such valuations seem to have come
Completely Stay
Wipro's sir will announce the results today along with the
Wipro to discuss buyback in meeting
Is There Something to Consider Before Results
Before the buyback or any other IT name
Sir, please look at Wipro.
Momentum is doing this and in fact maybe tomorrow
I also talked to Vivek Sir.
This was it, you would have continued this momentum.
It can be seen that it happened. Running on ₹2
and is maintaining above its 52 moving average
doing. Buyback price is very
It becomes important. where is this happening
Is. As soon as the announcement came, you saw it.
There was sustained buying in it from lower levels
It has been seen. Meaning, you see that this
We saw buying this a little in the month of F.
I had seen it a lot and now I am able to see it.
If you have a position and want to play
With a closing basis stop loss of 26
Please play. The results are good.
Positive news is created. Buyback Price
Looks good. Sustains of 26 and 216
After the movement, you will also get levels up to 232.
Can show.
Sir, please tell us about Tejas Network also.
The numbers have been bad. They are bad. Meaning
From profit this company went into loss.
I am saying this on a quarterly basis only.
Am. Down 4.5%. Sir very nice move
It showed it. 500 level should also be crossed
Had gone. You can get it now at 429. if someone
If you want to take it, avoid it or wait a little.
If you have to buy it then buy it. Sir, look at this
We have done Telecom Stocks with Telecom
Seen very often with equipment stocks
All of the Suns They Turn Around and Then
The situation seems to be getting worse.
Tejas Networks numbers are also very high
is not inspiring and the way in which
The fundamentals are also visible. You see these
After the numbers, price to book value also
It is visible very much. Dater does too much
are increasing more. Working capital does also
Are increasing. No, Tejas network is a
Complete avoidance. Do nothing right now
Needed
Okay, fine. Ok. Now we grow
Towards the primary market segment.
If you have any recent IPO
The question is, are you stuck on something or
Then you can check after recent correction or good
Considering that stock after the upmove
If so, please send us your question. We grow
Moving on to the primary market action.
[music]
Wow what an IPO [appreciation]
Sir, in the IPO segment there are two things which
I have to ask you. The first is property
This is the REIT of Share Investment Trust
Sir it is open from 10th and today its
It's the last day. This is fully subscribed so far
are done. 0.98 times this
The subscription has arrived. Now for retail
So it is not so sir. 10 lakh to 10.5 lakh
So there is a price band. Total shares are ₹330
Who are doing the issue. This is worth about Rs 245 crore.
They are collecting the surrounding amount of money. Sir in REET
In this, if someone has, say, 10 lakhs
You are also advised to invest a fund of around Rs.
Will you give?
Look, this is a very clear case sir. right now which
The entire situation seems to be developing in a way
Is. Do you need such a high ticket?
Should I invest? I a little bit
I will reframe. A little sense of comfort
I can see less. For now, avoid
I will say this and for the time being stay away.
Ok. You should stay away from this. don't make money from it
Apply it. Well the second one sir is an invite CTS
Trans Net Investment Trust. these days tomorrow
It will open from. Sorry. 17th to 21st
Its price range is ₹1105 crore
This is an issue. It is a fresh issue. ₹9 to ₹100
It has a price band that has been fixed.
Is. Sir, can I invest money in this?
I would have looked into its financials, sir. One
So it is not profitable. Is in loss.
Although the losses have been slightly higher over the periods of
If we look at the years, it is decreasing. right now which
The latest numbers we have are 9 for FY26.
Of months. ₹216 crore, loss of ₹19 crore
Theirs. Net worth is negative sir. and this
Negative is increasing sir negative
His net worth. Explain some numbers
And if you explain this a little bit, sir.
Invest money or not. Sir, please see the clear case.
Isn't it true that if you just look at the financials
So this also means reads like these then real estate
what happens is inbit
Infrastructure is financially supported
Are not in a position to take care of
Doing Things in Proper Manner and Net Worth
It is negative, meaning their dept is already so
The way it is higher at the two lower levels
You see this day's float that is visible
He is not giving me comfort and because of this I am also
I would say it is wise to maintain distance.
It will be about.
Ok, good. Let's take a look at some of the audience
Questions about recent IPOs in this segment
I would definitely like to take one or two
If you address the question in this. Karero
India Sir, a question has come regarding this, Shubham
Please forgive Subhash Mehta ji. Kare India
Saying I have 21 shares ₹704
At the time rate of. I will buy it at the time of IPO.
I am holding from. Show me once.
CA Double R ARO Cero India is at ₹617
Sir. Its price is ₹704. to review
I am asking you for this.
Sir, look, he has no momentum yet.
Shown in recent times. infact you
Let's see tomorrow and the day after tomorrow's trading sessions
I too have created an amazing movement in the way
Has come. I understand this movement now.
This should be continued. As long as these 581
Maintaining the above. may be coming
In the coming days you will also get up to 664 680
Show me the levels. For the Time Being 580K
Maintain the position with stop loss.
Ok. Ok. The other name is Sir.
of UTL Solar. Ask this Shalini Gupta ji
Have been. saying that they are for allotment
UTL Solar 845 shares. What Should Be Done?
He is 845 years old, sir. These
There are 845 shares. I think sir.
Fujiyama is talking about power.
Yes yes. UTL Solar is the same. Fujiyama Power.
Look, it has given movement but I am a
Cheez Aapko Bole Doon 14 Times Price to Book
The value is moving. A numbers slowly
I am getting better by doing it. Now you see what it means
Let me tell you that one side movement
He will do it or not.
Do you want it back to a lower level?
Can you show it? But the way you hold it
You are a long term investor
Are. Give it one quarter's time
This situation seems to be creating a way
Is. Maybe this momentum will give you a little
And show the upside. But very promising
This stock doesn't seem to be there. So I am very
Meaning because you are saying 800 odds
If you have a position at the levels, then I
I don't even understand how you exist.
Will you take it?
He has that many shares. from 854 shares
and price
Sir, he did not tell the price. I think
from the IPO price.
Ah sir I am so sorry I don't remember
IPO Price Pooja Power.
Let me tell you its price. Sir
Meanwhile, the price of one 172 was CM
of papdi. Sir, we also discussed IPO.
It was a subsidiary of Coal India. These 172
The one is still standing around 170. This
A question has come regarding this. Ah Atul Som ji
to say
Sorry sir, I mean I will interrupt you. A 228
Levels per your Fujiyama power per your if
If you have installed it then do one thing. now it
Gives me a very good sense of comfort. Now
I am getting some response.
You can trade this or I will trade this with a stop loss of 224
Let me advise you one more thing, if you age a little
Conservative investors or traders
264 levels found, you give your 200 shares
Please give it. 274 276 levels reached 200 more shares
Please give it to me. And sell your shares till 288 levels
Please keep the remaining 200. Well you
Booked profit and comfortably traded those shares
Let it lie there. Then
Ok. OK, that's perfect. Come now, sir.
at CMPDI. on CMDI like I did
You have received this question from Atul Som ji.
Its issue price was ₹172.
This stock is standing around ₹170. Now this
Asking if there is a new listing. Good
Profitable exit can be found in this
What? 10% 20% with a good profitable exit
Sir, please tell me as per your understanding. Look, I
I will tell them one thing that if you mean
Because you've still held on and
The way the whole situation is, if you
Give him two to three quarters
This may also make you a rerating candidate.
It should appear to be being made, meaning I will tell you for this
I will tell you one thing today, you may come
This thing can be seen in the coming days.
that it's anywhere from 200 to 40-50 levels if
After the movement was done, these brokerages
to get on the radar and all that.
Rerating will also start, become a candidate
Will go. Because we told you one thing
She said that if you look at its business
Neither are these mining companies nor metal
You are seeing companies or all these, right?
Consultancy and government approvals for
This is a very good work. That is why we gave you
IPO also if you are medium to long term
If you are an investor then I told you to invest.
This will bring you great benefits in the days to come.
Will give returns. Don't think about 10, 15, 20%.
This will also make you a multibagger in the long term.
It may appear to have happened.
Ok. One last question to Sir Amir Chand
Taking. The IPO of Amir Chand that came, right?
Its price was fixed at ₹212. Now
100 for Amir Chand
Singh Saheb has 500 shares at the rate of ₹26
Near. What should be done in this?
Look at Amir Chand. Your price
It is going on nearby. Now give it two
You have the option. Either you name it 116
Place a stop loss of and buy it now
Continue because in this we still
It becomes very important for us to
See how the numbers appear
Have been. And if you look at its chartical
If you look at the patterns then the 10th
Volume was on April, April 8th
There was volume and selling in that volume
I saw her coming. right now you
It definitely looks a bit risqué but
Volume base confirmation is not visible
Used to be. One bar with a stop loss of 116
Please play. Let's see how far it goes
It goes, how it is made. then a
Please come back and ask questions. We you
Will give an update.
So sir if the issue price is ₹212
They have taken a dip below 126
nearby. Well, they didn't do that, did they?
That I caught the falling knife. No sir, right now
At the very face of it, it's a bit wrong to say
It will happen because of the valuation correction
You've got to see it. The company is so bad
Not there.
The company is fine and whatever threats we see
It was being feared that this problem would arise in exports.
Will go. If geopolitics gets it right
So after that exports also normalize
You will see it happening. in the Middle East
As soon as the situation improves, you will be there too.
See, Indian Basmati has such a big market.
That definitely things are going to be okay for you.
Will be visible. Then let's go to perfect. ok then
Actually, we will wind up the IPO here again.
We do.
[music]
Wow, what an IPO? [Appreciation]
Before I wind up the show sir.
I must ask you one last question.
I would like to. That is regarding MTA Tech. MT
AR Tech which is a defensive play. Sanjeev
This is also Suri ji's question. On Facebook
The question is. They say analyze it
Give it. MTA Sir, you see today you are down 3%
It is visible. Please YT this
If you can show me the chart for this year
Sir, this 3% fall today is only this year.
Meaning we are sitting in the month of April, sir.
3 months have passed in this whole year so far
I am talking about the calendar year 2026.
Sir, 99.68% in this entire year
The return is 100%, it has already been done sir, it should be doubled.
It has been only within these 3 months that I
Do you remember Sir, the day when the budget was presented was on 1st February?
Lokesh ji at our rate of ₹2700
I was talking to him, he had said that this
You should buy stocks and continue
He keeps saying that in this you are buying
Make your position and sir how much time has passed
Is there a budget? It's been around 2 months
And in the 2nd month, see that 2700 becomes 270.
Went. The movement of 2000 has already come to its head.
Sir, why has this movement come up in M.Tech now?
Is? Is there a story behind this and what to do?
What is?
Sir, look at this, you just use it as a
Can't take it as a defense play.
In this, neither one nor the other is included in their business segment.
Clearly, civil nuclear power is also a very
It's a big thing. Fuel cells are done, hydel is done
gone, is also in space technology,
It is also in aerospace. There is also defense. We
Usually this is called defence. But
Sir, if you look at the clean energy space
36% of their revenue comes from there. And
Fuel cells, hydels and all that is included in it.
28% revenue comes. Space Technology 9%
The difference is only 2%. And this thing is a
It remains to be seen whether the company is already so
Dealing in innovative product line up
Is. A momentum that is visible.
In this momentum, I understand that now whatever
The results will come and you will get them somewhere or the other.
Will also be seen justifying the momentum.
Because if I look at the volumes, sir
Institutional to Retail Participation
Participation is seen changing hands
Used to be. Now what is the word of caution in this?
It will happen that after so much movement the price to
The book value has increased 20 times. But
It may be that he is somewhere else due to the result.
Let me show you the adjustments being made. So now
I will tell them that of course I am
Pretty sure you are not at these levels.
Must have taken it. taken at lower levels and
This could be the way the flight took place.
You can see further movement in it.
But after so much movement, one
Stop loss is a very important thing
4160 or let's round it up a little bit
Gives ₹4000 for safe haves
With a closing basis stop loss you
Maintain your position, whatever this momentum is
Showing if the results are good
So you will also get levels from ₹5400 to ₹5900.
It has the power to show off.
Ok sir. If I can find a reason for this
I try as much as my little limited
I have knowledge. Sir, on 6th April we made history.
It was created by India. After Russia, we are second
became the country that had this nuclear
reactor, this fast breeder reactor, which would have been
This is what we call FBR or PFBR.
One of our sirs is doing research in Tamil Nadu.
Baba has been in the Atomic Research Centre
In which we probably had I think 38 to 48 years old
For the first time since then, this project which
When did this research start?
After that we have achieved criticality, sir.
This is a technical term, I have given it a meaning.
I also saw a video about it.
Is this the thing, sir, that is in uranium?
Uranium as a fuel when we use
So one quality of uranium is that it chains
The reaction that occurs is that the fuel automatically
Ready to fuel yourself again
Keeps doing it. But criticality for that
It is very important to achieve. and in that
Thorium also has a significant contribution. Sir
Thorium is also so useful in itself or
There is not much active metal or compound.
But when it was mixed with uranium
Think uranium 223 something like that is his number.
When that thorium comes into that form. So
Thorium is equally active and useful.
It becomes as much as our uranium reserves
Overall, this chain reaction results in further uranium
The matter is stuck on enrichment only, Sir Iran.
The US one which is under discussion for enrichment
So this is the criticality that we have achieved
Sir, after Russia, we are the second country which
that these are made for nuclear power
Sir, we have created history and we can also benefit from it.
MTATech has got it somewhere
Sir, you mute Sir, if I say this now
Otherwise it would not have happened that this man
It drags things out so long. That's why I
I just gave you this little diversion so that you
Don't think of it as just a defense play and
This civil nuclear power is 36%
He does his revenue generation in a very
It is a big game changer. Sir, this is the news
It is important and further development is also important for you.
It will be seen happening in this. That's why Mtar
Our bullish take on technologies right now
We are running it after maintaining it.
MTAR has a lot of power. Ok. Very
Thank you sir. Thank you so much. This
Let's end the show here on a positive note.
Are. There was a lot of discussion about stocks
Yes sir. We have discussed the sectors.
Any disclaimer before I go, sir?
Absolutely sir. As many stocks as your channel
But discussed my personal position in it
Made family position, be client position
Can. All the stocks on your channel
We have discussed those companies and their promoters.
Groups, companies can be our clients.
Investment in Equity Market
Subject to market risk. please consult
Your Financial Advisor Before Making Any
Investing and Taking Any Trade in Any
of the scripts that we have discussed on
Your channel. Age always sir fun doing show early
I will meet you now. Let's go [laughs].
Ok sir. Same here sir, it's a lot of fun
By talking to you. Let's thank you for your time
To give. Wish you a very good day sir. So
We would wind up the opening bus right here.
Are. I am taking your permission. Hello.